<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>Holy.li</title><subtitle>My non-linear personal web notebook</subtitle><link href="holy.li/atom.xml" rel="self"></link><link href="holy.li"></link><author><name>Timofey</name></author><id>2b1f62e0-55ce-4440-72f2-f4e822ae5564</id><updated>2020-05-05T14:04:41</updated><entry><title>Hello world</title><link href="holy.li/#Hello%20world"></link><link href="holy.li/static/Hello%2520world.html" rel="alternative" type="text/html"></link><id>3e25960a-79db-c69b-674c-d4ec67a72c62</id><updated>2020-05-03T21:37:30</updated><content type="xhtml"><div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"><h2 class="">Hello</h2><p>This is my first post on this <a class="tc-tiddlylink-external" href="https://tiddlywiki.com/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">TiddlyWiki</a> blog!</p><h2 class="">What is TiddlyWiki?</h2><p>TiddlyWiki is all-in-one solution for blogging, taking notes and saving knowledge. It is better than any CMS or static site generator. TiddlyWiki is a self-contained html file that can be run in any browser. Even offline!</p><h2 class="">What can you do with it?</h2><p>TiddlyWiki is all about representing content in different ways. You can organize your thoughts however you like. Everything is dynamic and <em>reactive</em>. </p><p>For example, putting<br></br>
<code>&lt;$edit-text tiddler=&quot;$:/SiteSubtitle&quot; default=&quot;&quot; tag=&quot;input&quot;/&gt;</code>
<br></br>
in tiddler markup will embed input box with the name of this notebook. Try changing it! </p><p>Site name:  <input value="Holy.li"></input><br></br></p><p><strong>Everything is a tiddler.</strong> The page you are looking at is composed of hundreds of small tiddlers containing scripts, macros, templates, images and markup. This leads to extreme levels of customization and versatility while working with your own copy of TiddlyWiki.
Tiddlers are organized with so you can easily navigate around your stuff.</p><p>Now try changing site's color palette using buttons below.</p><p><span class="tc-popup-keep"><button aria-label="palette" class="" title="Choose the colour palette"> </button></span><span class=" tc-reveal" hidden="true"></span> <button class="">Reset palette</button></p><h2 class="">Any controversial moments?</h2><p>(Writing this while implementing theme toggler)</p><ul><li>Using macros and widgets feels like functional programming with pattern matching, no side effects and weird syntax :p</li><li>Too much to learn at once when you start hacking deep into your TiddlyWiki.</li></ul><p>On the other hand, the <a class="tc-tiddlylink-external" href="https://tiddlywiki.com" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">documentation</a> is <strong>awesome</strong>. Every single thing is fully documented with lots of examples you can poke around.</p><hr></hr><p>To summarize, TiddlyWiki is a great piece of software. This blog was actually inspired by <a class="tc-tiddlylink-external" href="https://joearms.github.io/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Joe Armstrong's TiddlyWiki notebook</a>. Joe was one of the creators of Erlang, but unfortunately, he is no longer with us.</p><p>Let me know what you think using email on <a class="tc-tiddlylink tc-tiddlylink-resolves" href="#About">About</a> page.</p></div></content><author><name>Timofey</name></author></entry></feed>

